I will talk about Punjab National Bank, so this
juice ad Bano time prem, so as I
told you yesterday that even though this
Punjab National Bank share is
falling slowly, you can see from these days, but the thing that
I told you that whenever it started falling, it was
above its all-time high, the
area which is in red color, you can see,
this is its time and the biggest
reference area, okay, and not only time,
sorry, it is its 52-week high, so from here the
last time the fall started from here, it had
fallen before that too and the
share had fallen from here for a long time before this too, okay, so the
question of buying in this area does
not arise, okay, whoever has paid by,
if someone is not buying the share in tempered glass, then
sell it here right now, book your loss, whatever it is, it is
not Vikas, look, this is what
I have reserved below, this is the demand for the share somewhere,
okay, and now we
can also call it zone,
okay, if you look here,
I have shown you a little bit of it, see, see this, see, I have shown you this.  So how many times has there been a
lot of difference in the share from here, the first
time it went up, the second time it went
up a lot, a little time it went up a lot, that time
boss, then the first time it went down, okay, it
came up again and from here a lot that it
talked from here only on the seventh or eighth
and this time also the share is coming around this area,
so what do I understand that
if my share is passbook around Rs 41
or around this area for seven or eight times, then
what should I do, at least right now the
share is at 41 or 80 paise, so I should
wait till it reaches Rs 41 in proximity, if
my share goes below 41 paise,
I will think of separating from the money, if I do
not get any support there,
but for now I should
fold till here, why should I do it,
Vikas already, whenever my share
comes around Rs 41, definitely a huge back comes from here, only then it goes
to the lock and the
maximum that goes by all, okay
and similarly, as many times my share is in this area,
it should fold on its bar  Seriously, it has become my lion and has gone up a
lot, so this time too it is
possible that again somewhere or the other this
lion of mine 41 touches it and goes up to 2445, you
can see that, okay, so for
now I should not sell,
I should wait here, 41 is my lion at the same price,
store okay, I should
wait for the share to come in this zone,
if my share takes support from the bottom in this area and
turns upwards again, then definitely you will be unaware of my words
and slowly as my share
comes down from here, it is watching me, similarly from
here as it went up, you
can see it going up from here also, okay, so definitely
set it till here, do not book a loss by selling, this is
from the gang, okay, so like Jal Board Punjab National
Bank, okay, this is the folder 151 and if you
have to press buy, then you will do it only
if the share sustains in this area and
starts giving a positive moment, okay, okay, okay, I
understood, and we will talk a
little about the target, if you see, today  The
stock has been flat, okay, there has
not been a big fall
of Rs 143, whoever saw 141,
see the graph of 50 paise, if it fell yesterday then the first
target is downwards, if there is a further
fall beyond this in the zone of 241, I think I
know that even after taking support,
maximum times it took support here,
okay, if it turns upwards then the
pack is already there and the second one is Rs 21
paise, I said that the third one is also a man, so
you can definitely see all this around 50 paise,
okay, so D'Souza is
Punjab National Bank peon, suggest when a little
she, don't sell in panic